Amanda Steele Show. Today goes to Black Southern churchgoers for feeling seen during the Super Bowl.
Hallelujah. Hallelujah. Now you might be asking, Amanda, where was there anything churchworthy
in the Super Bowl? Now, Usher drew millions of viewers for his halftime performance,
but it was Jermaine Dupri's knitted woolen, pearly white Louis Vuitton socks that made
all the Southern churchgoers have flashbacks to their childhoods when they donned those very
socks during Easter Sunday. Evangelists, Deaconesses, all had glee from the nostalgia,
but found it preposterous that these foot covers were made by Louis Vuitton when they could have
easily been rented or borrowed from a Southern grandma's drawer of bloomers. Yeah, right.
So shout out to those socks. It gave sockitamy a new meaning. Today's letdown.
Goes to mind-boggling, head-scratching excuses. Page Six reports that Justin Bieber was indeed
invited by Usher, Usher, Usher to be part of his Super Bowl halftime performance, and he declined.
An insider explained, there's no bad blood between Usher and Justin. Justin just wasn't up for it.
Just wasn't feeling it. I just feel like you got to give more of an excuse than that when you turn
down like the literal invite to perform at the Super Bowl. I'm not sure what he would have added to
the performance anyway, though. I think it was solid in who came out. You know, I think Usher has
definitely something to be proud of.
We are